http://www.allergy.org.au/about-ascia/disclaimer-and-privacy#copyright

Health Professionals
ASCIA Action Plans, First Aid Plans, Treatment Plans and Checklists
ASCIA Guidelines Acute management of anaphylaxis
ASCIA Guidelines Acute Management of Anaphylaxis in Pregnancy
ASCIA Guidelines for the prevention of anaphylaxis in schools, preschools and childcare
Hereditary Angioedema (HAE) References
Subcutaneous Immunoglobulin (SCIg)
ASCIA SCIg Treatment Plan
ASCIA Transfer Care Plan - IRT
ASCIA Travel Plan for SCIg Patients
Guide – Setting up a Subcutaneous Immunoglobulin (SCIg) program in a hospital
ASCIA Guidelines for standardised IVIg infusion rates for IRT
ASCIA ID Register Access Film
ASCIA Guidelines: Vaccination of the egg-allergic individual
External position papers
Australian Airborne Pollen and Spore Monitoring Network Interim Standard and Protocols
Drug allergy
Drug Allergy (Medication)
Anaphylaxis e-training feedback
Anaphylaxis e-training first aid (community)
Drug Allergy
Eczema (Atopic Dermatitis)
Eczema and Food Allergy
Food Allergy
Hay Fever (Allergic Rhinitis)
Allergy and anaphylaxis
What is allergy?
Allergic rhinitis (hay fever) and sinusitis
Allergic rhinitis (hay fever)?
ASCIA Eczema Action Plan
Hives (urticaria)
Orofacial granulomatosis
Allergy prevention
Allergy prevention
ASCIA Information on how to introduce solid foods to babies for allergy prevention
Allergy prevention frequently asked questions (FAQs)
Autoimmunity overview
Systemic Lupus Erythematosus (SLE)
ASCIA Dietary avoidance for food allergy
Cow's milk protein (dairy)
Food intolerance
Food Protein-Induced Allergic Proctocolitis (FPIAP)
Food protein induced enterocolitis syndrome (FPIES)
COVID-19, Immunodeficiency and School Attendance
Subcutaneous immunoglobulin (SCIg) therapy - general information
Subcutaneous immunoglobulin (SCIg) therapy - equipment checklist
Subcutaneous immunoglobulin (SCIg) infusion checklist
Immunoglobulin replacement therapy
Primary Immunodeficiency (PIDs)
Severe combined immunodeficiency
Common variable immune deficiency (CVID)
Insect allergy (bites and stings)
Published Abstracts ASCIA
Annual Conferences (1990 onwards)
Health Professionals
ASCIA Action Plans, First Aid Plans, Treatment Plans and Checklists
Anaphylaxis e-training
Anaphylaxis e-training first aid (community)
Immunodeficiencies
Insect allergy (bites and stings)
Disclaimer
Information provided by Australasian Society of Clinical Immunology and Allergy (ASCIA) on its website is for educational, communication and information purposes only and is not intended to replace or constitute medical advice or treatments.
It is the intenion of ASCIA that all information contained on this website is accurate. Education materials contained on this website have been reviewed and approved by ASCIA members, including those on appropriate ASCIA committees. However, errors sometimes occur. Therefore, ASCIA disclaims any warranty of any kind, whether express or implied, as to any matter whatsoever relating to this service, including without limitation merchantability or fitness for any particular purpose. In no event shall ASCIA be liable for any indirect, special, incidental or consequential damages arising out of any use of or reliance on any content or materials contained herein.
In accordance with the Health on the Net Code of Conduct, ASCIA adheres to the following principles:
Authority:Any medical or health advice provided and hosted on this website will only be given by medically trained and qualified professionals unless a clear statement is made that a piece of advice offered is from a non-medically qualified individual or organisation.
Confidentiality:Confidentiality of data relating to individual patients and visitors to a medical/health Web site, including their identity, is respected by this website. The website owners undertake to honour or exceed the legal requirements of medical/health information privacy that apply in the country and state where the website and mirror sites are located.
Attribution:Where appropriate, information contained on this website will be supported by clear references to source data and, where possible, specific HTML links to that data. The date when a clinical page was last modified will be clearly displayed (e.g. at the bottom of the page).
Transparency of Sponsorship:The ASCIA website is directly funded by ASCIA and therefore ASCIA does not seek nor receive any educational grants to fund this website. Hence there are no conflicts of interest regarding the sources of funding and the editorial content of the website. Support for specific projects (e.g. ASCIA e-training courses) from unrestricted educational grants is clearly identified, including the identities of commercial and non-commercial organisations that have contributed funding, services or material for the relevant webpages.
ASCIA does not assume and hereby disclaims any and all liability to any person or entity for any claims, damages, liability or other loss including, without limitation, any liability for injury or other damage resulting from any use of or reliance on this service, or from the posting of any content or material by any third party. No use of, or reliance on, any materials included in this website shall be deemed to give rise to a medical practitioner-patient relationship. No material included in this website shall be deemed to present the only or necessarily the best method or procedure with respect to a matter discussed on this service; rather, any such material shall be acknowledged as only the approach or opinion of the discussant. The user assumes all risks of using the materials included in this website.
Editorial Policy
The website is for use by the general public and health professionals.
The health information content provided on this website is developed by the members of ASCIA who are medical and allied health professionals. The health information presented such as guidelines and educational materials are based on current medical knowledge and practice as at the date of publication.
Web Medical Editorial Responsibility
Information for this website is developed and approved by ASCIA Committee and Working Party Members.  Any questions should be directed to This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Webmaster
Impagination  This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Copyright
Copyrights to the materials included in this website are owned solely by the ASCIA, except for materials which are created by others (or the copyright to which is otherwise owned by others) and for which a copyright notice is posted adjacent to such content or materials. The copyright to each item of material created or otherwise owned by another is owned by such creator or other owner. None of the materials included in this website may be reproduced in any form without the express written permission of ASCIA, the creator or other owner, as the case may be. In this regard, the graphic images and layout of this site are the exclusive property of ASCIA and may not be copied, distributed or displayed except using an HTML browser or as otherwise stated herein, without the express written permission of the ASCIA.
Permission is hereby granted to (1) print copies of the materials for which the ASCIA holds the copyright, for personal and non-commercial use and only for informational purposes.
Except as stated herein, no portion of the materials included in this website may be reproduced or transmitted in any form by any means, whether by electronic, mechanical, photocopying, recording or otherwise, without the written permission of the ASCIA.
Privacy Statement
When you visit the ASCIA website, ASCIA will not collect personally identifiable information about you, unless such information is provided voluntarily by you. The personally identifiable information collected by ASCIA is strictly confidential and ASCIA will not reveal, disclose, sell, distribute, share or otherwise pass on to any third parties any personal information that you may have provided unless permitted by law or ASCIA has your express written consent to do so. You should also be aware that non-personal information and data might be automatically collected through the use of "cookies". Cookies are pieces of information that a website can use to recognise repeated usage, facilitate the users on getting access to and use of the website and allow a website to track usage behaviour and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvement and targeted advertising. The use of cookies is standard and you will find that most websites use them. Most Internet browsers are preset to accept cookies. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can adjust your Internet browser to refuse cookies or to warn you when cookies are being used.
Currently we are using Google Analytics to analyse the audience of the website and improve our content. No personal information is collected from Google Analytics. For further information on the privacy policy concerning Google Analytics go to www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html
Links
This website contains links to third party websites. These linked websites are not under the control of ASCIA and ASCIA is therefore not responsible for the contents of any linked websites or any hyperlink contained in any linked websites. ASCIA provides these links as a convenience only and the inclusion of any link does not imply any endorsement of the linked website by ASCIA. You link to any linked websites entirely at your own risk.
Virus warning
ASCIA does not represent or warrant that any files obtained from or through this website are free from computer viruses or other defects. Any such files are provided and may be used on the basis that the user accepts all responsibility for any loss, damage or other consequence resulting directly or indirectly from the use of those files.
Inquiries regarding usage of the ASCIA trademarks or copyrights or the trademarks and copyrights of others which are contained in this website should be emailed to This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Content updated January 2018
Print
About ASCIA
About ASCIA
About Clinical Immunology and Allergy
About ASCIA e-training
AIFA
ASCIA Collaborations
Log in
Forgot your password?
Forgot your username?
ASCIA Update
Information for the community about allergic diseases, immunodeficiencies and other immune diseases.See latest edition here...Join our mailing list:
ASCIA News
ASCIA Oral Immunotherapy (OIT) for Food Allergy Update
AIFA Research Grants 2020
Updated ASCIA FAQ How to Introduce Solid Foods for Allergy Prevention
ASCIA COVID-19 update
ASCIA Immunodeficiency Strategy for Australia and New Zealand
About ASCIA
ASCIA is the peak professional body of clinical immunology and allergy in Australia and New Zealand ASCIA promotes and advances the study and knowledge of allergy and other immune diseases
Quick Links
Anaphylaxis resources
Action/treatment plans
ASCIA Annual Conferences
Locate a specialist
Patient information
Health professionals
ASCIA e-training
Immunodeficiency
Drug allergy
Hay fever|asthma
Food allergy
Allergy and the skin
About ASCIA
ASCIA is a registered trademark of the Australasian Society of Clinical Immunology and Allergy. All content is subject to copyright for the Australasian Society of Clinical Immunology and Allergy. Read more...
The content for the website is developed and approved by ASCIA Committee and ASCIA Working Party Members. Read more...
Disclaimer I Privacy
The ASCIA website is intended for use by ASCIA members, health professionals and the general public. The content provided is for education, communication and information purposes only and is not intended to replace or constitute medical advice or treatments. Read more...
ASCIA respects your privacy. Read our privacy policy here...
Sponsors | Advertising
ASCIA does not endorse products from sponsoring organisations, nor is it influenced by sponsoring organisations with regard to the content of education programs and websites.
The ASCIA website does not accept advertising. Any link to a third-party website does not imply any endorsement by ASCIA.
Accreditiation
This site complies with the
HONcode standard for trustworthy health information: verify here.
Sitemap
Feedback
©   ASCIA 2020
Website by Impagination
